<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Martin Clement Wins PPTQ - Common Ground Games!</title>
      <pubDate>4th December 2016</pubDate>
      <description> Martin "Mush" Clement calls upon his friends to lend him some Stern Constables so he can attend his first and Scotland's last PPTQ of the season and win it. He did not disappoint. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Deane Wins PPTQ - Bus Stop Toy Shop!</title>
      <pubDate>3rd December 2016</pubDate>
      <description> Peter Deane gathers as much energy as he can to RG Aetherworks Marvel his way through some insane board states to take down the Bus Stop Toy Shop PPTQ in Largs, formerly owned by Duncan Tang. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drew Martin Wins PPTQ - Abbey Games!</title>
      <pubDate>27th November 2016</pubDate>
      <description> 
        . </description>
    </item>
     <item>
      <title>Dani Anderson Wins PPTQ - Highlander Games!</title>
      <pubDate>26th November 2016</pubDate>
      <description> 
       Dani pilots Mardu Vehicles through the field at Highlander Games to win an RPTQ Invite!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martin "Harry" Porter Wins PPTQ RS Dyga!</title>
      <pubDate>13th November 2016</pubDate>
      <description> 
       Harry travels 3 hours all by his lonesome to RS Dyga in Inverness to find there are only 7 people registered. A quick call to Scotland legend Gary Campbell and they have an event! Martin pilots his Blue White staples to victory and will be joining the other qualified players! </description>
    </item>
  	<item>
      <title>Wayne Dillon Wins PPTQ Murphy's Vault</title>
      <pubDate>5th November 2016</pubDate>
      <description> 
       Wayne travels to Edinburgh and fights his way through the Murphy's Vault team with UW Flash to the finals of PPTQ Murphy's Vault! His opponent concedes in favour of prize support rather than an invite to the RPTQ! Classic Wayne! </description>
    </item>
  	<item>
      <title>Neil MacGregor Wins PPTQ Geek Retreat</title>
      <pubDate>30 October 2016</pubDate>
      <description> Neil MacGregor went undefeated in the swiss and beat his team mates to victory in top 8 to earn himself an invite to the RPTQ  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael McMenamin Wins PPTQ Settlers</title>
      <pubDate>16 October 2016</pubDate>
      <description> Michael McMenamin managed to 4 main deck negate his way through 5 rounds of swiss and 3 rounds of Top 8 to victory at Settlers in Hamilton.
       Calum Williams made both finals this weekend for the first PPTQ weekend of this season. All he needs is a little luck to get there! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duncan Wins PPTQ Spellbound</title>
      <pubDate>15 October 2016</pubDate>
      <description> The PPTQ Season has started for Kaladesh Standard! Duncan plays small men and big ships to smash his way through to victory over Calum Williams in the finals! Due to this qualification, Duncan Tang can no longer win the PPTQ Bus Stop Toy Shop breaking his near 100% win rate at that PPTQ each season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Gotlib Wins PPTQ Aberdeen</title>
      <pubDate>3 October 2016</pubDate>
      <description> Nathan Gotlib travelled far to attend the last PPTQ of the season in Scotland. The format was Sealed Kaladesh and Nathan managed to crew his way into top 8 and a PPTQ victory! Nathan joins the other PPTQ winners of the season for a chance at a Pro Tour Invitation in December, congratulations Nathan! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Scotland Confirmed!</title>
      <link>http://www.tsangtuary.com</link>
      <pubDate>29 September 2016</pubDate>
      <description>Brandon Balfour, Kevin Pass, Marc Ferguson and captain Stephen Murray will be taking us to victory at the World Magic Cup! </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>